Tufts Sports UP147
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Sports
1995 -- 2000
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of Physical Education
UP147
1.2 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains quarterly issues of Tufts Sports from 1995-2000. It was published quarterly by Tufts Athletics for alumni, parents and friends of Jumbo sports.
- Tufts Sports, 1995 -- 2000; UP147.001; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Tufts Sports which was published quarterly by Tufts Athletics for alumni, parents and friends of Jumbo sports.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Sports, Fall/Winter, 1995; UP147.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Summer/Fall, 1996; UP147.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Spring/Summer, 1996; UP147.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Winter/Spring, 1996; UP147.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Fall/Winter, 1996; UP147.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Winter/Spring, 1997; UP147.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Spring/Summer, 1997; UP147.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Fall/Winter, 1997 -- 1998; UP147.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Summer, 1998; UP147.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Fall/Winter, 1998 -- 1999; UP147.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Summer, 1999; UP147.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Fall/Winter, 1999 -- 2000; UP147.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Sports, Spring/Summer, 2000; UP147.001.001.00013 (Box 1)